<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CricFen</string>
    <string name="news_dummy_content">The triumphant Aussies had a big night of celebrations in store after their 19-run win over South Africa in Sunday’s ICC Women’s T20 World Cup final at Newlands.
\n\n
But the party kicked off on the field, with plenty of the winning team speaking about their third T20 win in succession – or the ‘threepeat’ as it has been coined back home.
\n\n
“We have been longing for this moment since the last World Cup,” Player of the Tournament Ash Gardner said.
\n\n
“We played some fantastic cricket throughout the tournament. Today just showed that we were not in winning positions throughout the game, but we scrapped and we fought.</string>

    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>

    <string name="onboarding_title_1">All in one app for the billions of Cricket fans.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_description_1">Get all Cricket contents &amp; services at CricFen, just catch it free.</string>

    <string name="onboarding_title_2">Easy to book Cricket match ticket.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_description_2">Get seamless ticket booking experience with 360 view features.</string>

    <string name="onboarding_title_3">Get delicious food at your seat in few minutes.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_description_3">stadium experience made easy with food &amp; beverage ordering feature.</string>

    <string name="onboarding_title_4">Great shopping experience for Cricket fans.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_description_4">Order your favourite team merchandise like Jerseys, T-shirts, Joggers &amp; more.</string>

    <string name="onboarding_title_5">Get chance to win exciting prizes via contests.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_description_5">Participate in contests &amp; get chance to win prizes as well as meet &amp; greets opportunity.</string>

    <string name="onboarding_title_6">Easy to buy &amp; sell Cricket memorabilia NFTs.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_description_6">Explore NFTs marketplace to buy &amp; sell Cricket memorabilia NFTs.</string>

    <string name="accept_condition_string">By logging in you agree to our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, including cookies use.</string>
    <string name="resend_otp">Don\'t receive the OPT? Resend OTP</string>
</resources>